No! Asuna!
Free?
No!
Let go of me, no!
Asuna! Asuna!
Asuna!
Run, Xenon!
Kirito...
What the hell?
Get off me!
Master, it's all your fault!
She's mine!
She's mine, damn it!
Stay away from her!
Kirito!
He got me.
It happened so fast.
I didn't even see the needle!
I know!
I'm gonna take a look, okay?
Hang on, I'm not gonna
let you die like this!
Um, hey, you got this
weird thing on your chest.
Please tell me that's where
you hit me with the needle.
It looks like it, I guess.
What is that thing anyway?
It's one of the electrodes from this
heart monitor I was hooked up to.
Heart monitor?
Never mind.
You know, you scared the hell out of me.
I scared you?
How do you think I feel?
I thought you were gonna
die just now, you dumbass!
Hey, easy!
He's not dead, is he?
No, he's still got a pulse.
You're crazy, but thank
you for coming over.
No, thank you for
clocking him when you did.
I'm sorry I couldn't get here sooner.
You okay?
I'm sorry.
I can't wait to see the look on her face.
I know, right?
Next time you want to meet, be on time.
Seriously?
Girl, you've been acting
way too cocky lately.
She's right.
We should teach you a lesson.
No you guys it's cool we're
all friends here, right?
It's good to have friends.
They come in real handy,
especially when you need a loan.
Speaking of, I need 20k, buddy!
I told you before, I'm not
lending you guys any money.
You'll change your mind after I
show you what my brother gave me.
I doubt it.
Get this, he told me not to point
this at anyone, but what does he know?
I mean, you've seen one before,
so it doesn't bug you, right?
Or does it, Asada?
Get on your knees and say you're sorry.
Crap, it's not working.
Ow!
Government issue M-1911.
Your brother has good taste.
It's not really my style, though.
And for future reference, it
only fires when the safety's off.
Hey, whoa!
Your brother's right.
You shouldn't point this at people.
Here.
Oh my god, are you okay?
Get up, Endo!
See you around.
They say the first step's
always the hardest.
Hey, Asada!
Do you know that guy?
Is he your boyfriend?
Really?
When I said I'd meet you, I didn't think
you'd part yourself in front of my school.
Hmm? Oh.
What's up, Sinon?
Kyoji Shinkawa and his older
brother Shoichi were arrested.
During the interrogation, it came
out that another person was involved.
This third death gun, Atsushi
Kanamoto, is still out there.
but Kikuoka says they'll
catch him soon enough.
They got the idea of creating
the Death Gun character when
Shoichi got the invisibility
cloak through a real money trade.
Using the cloak and some binoculars,
Shoichi started stealing the
real-world info of the other players.
Meanwhile, his little brother Kyochi was
having issues with his avatar, Spiegel.
These players who think it's
all about their agility?
Man, they're living in a dream.
Spiegel was an AGI type, which
Zexine used to recommend.
But Zexine shifted his stats to an
STR-VIT combo, and that pissed Kyoji off.
When Shoichi found out, he gave
Kyoji Zexine's name and address IRL.
Then, they started talking
about how to kill him.
They say they weren't
serious about it at first.
But day after day,
the more they talked about it, the more
it seemed they could get away with it.
For their plan to work, they needed
two things from their dad's hospital.
A master key card used to open doors in
emergencies, and a lethal drug for the deed.
They researched their victims carefully,
narrowing the list down to the ones who
lived alone in low-security apartments.
Using the key card, Shoichi broke
into their first victim's place,
Shigemura, a .k .a. Zekseed.
The brothers worked out the exact
time he was supposed to die.
when Kyoji logged in as his
brother's avatar Sterben
and announced himself as
Death Gun and shot Zexit.
Their second victim, Usushio
Tarako, was killed the same way.
But instead of being scared of Death Gun,
the other players in GGO treated
it like some kind of joke.
Shoichi and his partners were furious,
so they decided to kill some
players during the B .O .B.
final.
They found three who met the same
criteria as Zexit and Tarako,
Hailrider, Garrett, and Sinon.
Killing three people was going to make
things hard for just the two of them, though.
Yeah.
To be in sync with Death Gun,
the person doing the
real-world killing had to
make sure they'd be at each
target's house on time.
So they recruited that Kanamoto guy you
told me about to be the third Death Gun.
Where'd they find him, though? Simple.
Kanamoto was an old friend of Shoichi's.
They were both part of
Laughing Coffin and SAO.
We found out his handle
there was Johnny Black.
That sound familiar?
Yeah, he worked with Zaza.
I think his weapon of
choice was a poison knife.
They put Kanamoto on Pale Rider and
Garrett, because he lived nearby.
Sinon, on the other hand, was Kyoji's.
See, Shoichi was the one
who usually did the killing.
But for this one job, Kyoji
insisted on being the one to do it.
Um, is that what he wanted?
For real?
Did Shinka, I mean, Kyoji, say that? No.
His brother was the one who gave
us all the details of their plan.
Kyoji still refuses to talk.
He does, huh?
Speaking of, we found out a
little more about Shoichi.
Health-wise, he'd been
sickly since childhood.
His father pretty much gave up on him,
so he decided early on to hand
the hospital over to Kyoji.
Staying sharp, ma 'am.
Locked and loaded.
Even so, the brothers seemed
to be close growing up.
But then Shoichi got
obsessed with MMORPGs,
and in 2022, he got trapped
in Sword Art Online.
After he got out, Shoichi
only spoke to Kyoji about it.
He bragged about how in that
world he was a real mass murderer,
and how he was feared.
In Kyoji's eyes, his
big brother was a hero.
As for Shoichi,
he's sticking with the story that
everything about the Death Gun concept,
including the murders,
was just part of a game.
That his actions here, like
gathering intel on victims,
prepping for the murders, and committing
them, were no different than an SAO.
The dark side of VR Miss.
That's what it is.
his reality got a lot less real.
Yeah, good point.
And how are you handling yours?
I feel like I left a
part of me back in SAO.
So right now, there's less of
me here than there was before.
I don't know.
You don't know?
Do you want to go back? Seriously?
How could you ask me that?
Um, wait a sec.
You're kind of contradicting
what you told me the other day.
What?
You said there's no such thing
as a virtual world, remember?
That like, wherever you
were, that's your reality.
Where I am right now, here,
this world is my reality.
And even if you told me this was a virtual
world, it would still be reality to me.
You see what I mean?
I guess.
Yeah, you're right.
I gotta hand it to you, Sinon.
What you said just now might be the only
good thing to come out of this nightmare.
No, put a sock in it.
Sorry, I'm with Kirito on this one.
Well, I told you pretty much
all we've found out so far.
You have any questions before I go? I do.
Has there been any word on what's
going to happen to Kyoji yet?
Based on his brother's
confession and their behavior,
they'll most likely be sent
to a medical detention center.
I doubt either one knows
what reality is anymore.
No, I don't think that's true.
I don't know anything
about Kyochi's brother.
I never met him.
But I've known Kyochi a long time and, well,
I think his reality was Gungail Online.
He'd pretty much given up on this world.
There was nothing left for him other
than GGO, so he made that his reality.
He'd spend hours in it, grinding away,
boosting his XP and trying to be the best.
I guess the stress got
to be too much for him.
From playing a game?
I know you can lose track
of time, but reality? Sure.
At some point, Kyoji just swapped
out one for the other, his real life,
for his virtual one.
Okay, but why?
I don't know, but I wish I did.
Kirito, why do you think he did it?
To get stronger.
You're right.
I guess I was the same way.
When it comes down to it, maybe
all us VRMMO players are the same.
All we want is to get stronger.
Mr.
Kikwoka, I'd like to go see
him if that's all right.
There's so much I want to tell him,
like what we were just talking about.
And other stuff I've been
thinking, if it's okay.
You're a strong person to want to.
And I, for one, think it's a great idea.
He can't have visitors yet, but
when he can, I'll let you know.
Well, I have to get
back to the office now.
Okay.
Thanks for taking the time.
Yes, thank you for talking to us.
Don't even mention it.
You guys risked your lives, and
God knows how many you saved.
It's the least I could do.
Oh, by the way, Kirito,
Death Gun, or Shoichi Shinkawa,
or Red-Eyed Zaza, or whatever you want to
call him, asked me to give you a message.
If you don't want to hear it,
say the word and I'll tear it up.
I'll hear it.
You got it.
He wrote,
If you think this is over, it's not.
You don't have what it takes to end this.
Sooner or later, you'll realize that.
It's showtime.
That's it.
Hey, uh, Sinon? Hmm? What's up?
Are you free right now?
What do you mean, free?
Free for what?
So, this is where you're taking me? Yep.
There's someone inside I want you to meet.
Well, it's about time.
It made us wait so darn long, I wouldn't
have had two slices of apple pie.
If I get fat, it's all your fault.
How's that my fault? Jeez.
Come on, Kirito.
Are you going to introduce us or what?
Huh? Oh, right. Sorry.
This is Shino Asada, a .k .a. Sinon.
Gun Gale Online's third super champ.
Oh, don't say that.
These are my friends from my time in SAO.
Rika, a .k .a.
Liz, Blacksmith and Swindler. Huh?
What the hell did you call me?
And that's Asuna, the berserk healer.
Real name, Asuna Yuki.
Berserk?
You want to grab a seat
and get something to drink?
That's what Star...
I mean, sterben means?
A term hospitals use for death.
What was he thinking, giving
his avatar a name like that?
If I were you,
I wouldn't try to find some deeper
meaning in the name he gave his avatar.
A lot of times it boils down to
whatever a player thinks sounds cool.
Oh, that explains it.
This whole time I thought
you gave your avatar
your name because you lacked imagination.
Zip it!
I do so have imagination. Lots
of it! Okay, geez. Whatever.
So anyway, I'm super stoked you're here.
It's always cool to meet
another girl VRMMO player.
You said it.
I hope we can be great friends, Asura.
Listen, Asura. Shino.
There's another reason for us
asking you to come here today.
What is it?
Sinon, I'm sorry to put
you on the spot like this.
I, uh, I told Asuna and Liz about what
happened to you when you were younger.
I didn't have a choice.
I needed their help.
I'll explain.
We wanted to help you, so we paid a
visit to the town where you used to live.
How could you?
Why would you do that?
Wait, Sinon.
They found someone who wants to meet you.
I can't let you leave till you
hear what they have to say.
It might hurt, and I'm sorry.
But I can't stand by if there's
a chance what they say helps.
Who is this person?
What do they want to tell me?
Sari, do I know you?
Sachi Osawa, you're
Shino Asada, aren't you?
I'd like to introduce you to my daughter.
Her name's Miss.
She's four years old.
I don't know if you remember.
But I used to work at the post office.
I'm sorry.
This is really hard.
See, I…
I should have done this ages ago.
I'm so sorry it took this long.
I never apologized or
thanked you for what you did.
I was pregnant with her the day that
man came in and tried to rob us.
What you did, it wasn't
just my life you saved.
You saved the life of my little girl, too.
Thank you so much.
If it weren't for you,
she wouldn't be here.
I saved your daughter?
Xenon, time to let go.
You've been blaming yourself way too long,
Beating yourself up over what happened.
I'm not saying you're
wrong to do that, but...
It's just, whatever guilt
you feel about what you did,
you got a right to consider
the lives you saved, too.
You got the right to think about
those people and forgive yourself.
That's it.
That's what I wanted you to know.
I made it for you.
Thank you for saving Mommy!
And for saving me!
We love you.
Oh, my God.
I don't need
one more time.
I want to be stronger and stronger.
I want to be in the dark.
Next time, debriefing.